Minjung Kim

google scholar

minnjung.github.io github.com/minnjung

minjung.kim@vision.snu.ac.kr

317, Bldg 138, 1 Gwanak-ro, Gwanak-gu, Seoul, South Korea

Research Interests

My research interests are in the field of 3D Place Recognition and Visual Localization, especially about (i) understanding the scene from images and point clouds, (ii) dealing with cross-modalities, and (iii) utilizing high-level semantic information for place recognition.

Education

Integrated M.S./Ph.D. Student in Computer Science and Engineering

Mar. 2018 - Current

- Seoul National University, Seoul, South Korea
- Adviser: Prof. Gunhee Kim (Vision and Learning Laboratory)

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering

Mar. 2014 - Feb. 2018

- Sogang University, Seoul, South Korea
- Cumulative GPA: 3.58 / 4.3 (3.88 / 4.5), Magna Cum Laude

Publications

Indoor/Outdoor Transition Recognition Based on Door Detection Seohyun Jeon, Minjung Kim , Seunghwan Park, Jaeyoung Lee	UR, 2022
Drop-Bottleneck: Learning Discrete Compressed Representation for Noise-Robust Exploration Jaekyeom Kim, Minjung Kim , Dongyeon Woo, Gunhee Kim	ICLR, 2021
Logo Detection and Recognition Algorithm using YOLO-v3 Model Minjung Kim, Sungen Kim, Gunhee Kim	CICS, 2020
Memorization Precedes Generation: Learning Unsupervised GANs with Memory Networks Youngiin Kim. Miniung Kim . Gunhee Kim	ICLR, 2018

Work and Research Experiences

Teaching Assistant	2022-3 SK ML Engineer course	Nov. 2022 – Dec. 2022
Teaching Assistant	KDB AI course	April. 2022 – May. 2022
Teaching Assistant	LG Al core human resource training course	Feb. 2022
Teaching Assistant	Teaching assistant of Topics in Artificial Intelligence at Seoul National University	Sep. 2020 – Dec. 2020
Teaching Assistant	Teaching assistant of IoT·Artificial Intelligence·Big Data (IAB) at Seoul National University	Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2019
Teaching Assistant	Teaching assistant of Discrete Mathematics at Seoul National University	Mar. 2018 – Jun. 2018
Research Intern	Vision and Learning Laboratory at Seoul National University	Jul. 2017 – Feb. 2018
Research Intern	Biointelligence Laboratory at Seoul National University	Sep. 2016 – Feb. 2017
Kit Developer - Arduino & Raspberry Pi	MakeWith (Startup)	Dec. 2016 – Jan. 2017
Teaching Assistant	Teaching assistant of C & Python language and project design at Sogang University	Mar. 2016 – Dec. 2018
Admission Test Supervisor	Sogang University	Feb. 2015 – Feb. 2016

Projects

DeepGuider Apr. 2019 – Current

- To develop a navigation guidance system that enables robots to navigate in urban environment without the need of pre-mapping of the environment
- This research project is funded by the government

Awards and Scholarship

Samsung Humantech Paper Award	Feb. 2021
- Samsung Electronics	
- Silver Prize in Signal Processing	

KSC 2017 Paper Award Feb. 2018

- Korean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers

- Third Prize

Magna Cum Laude Honor at Sogang University Feb. 2018

Grade Scholarship at Sogang University

Jul. 2017 – Feb. 2018

The 10th Grade, Windows 10 IoT Core & Microsoft Azure for Microsoft IoT Solution Competition Apr. 2017

Intership Scholarship at Sogang University

Dec. 2016 – Jan. 2017

Admission Test Work Scholarship at Sogang University

Nov. 2015 – Nov. 2016

Professional Activities

2022-3 SK Engineer Technical Coaching	Feb. 2023
Reviewer	CVPR, 2023
Reviewer	ICLR, 2023
Reviewer	ACCV, 2022
Reviewer	NeurlPS, 2022
Reviewer	ICLR, 2022
Reviewer	NeurIPS, 2021